<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Aprenda a fazer tudo!</title>
        <link>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Aprenda a fazer tudo!</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 01:31:07 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>How install to iTunes 2020 - Step by Step</title>
    <link>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-instalar-itunes-2020/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 01:31:07 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-instalar-itunes-2020/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[iTunes is the easiest way to enjoy everything you need for your entertainment: music, movies and TV shows and keep it all organized easily. Rent or buy movies, download your favorite TV shows and more. ITunes is also home to Apple Music, where you can listen to millions of songs and your entire music library, completely without commercial ads.
1. Downloading iTunes Access the website click here to download iTunes click the &ldquo;Download Google Drive&rdquo; button (2nd option click here).]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to convert and download a YouTube video into music</title>
    <link>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/youtube-conversao-mp3/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 02:03:38 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/youtube-conversao-mp3/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[YouTube is a video sharing platform.
1. Accessing YouTube Access the official page of YouTube. YouTube pageYouTube
" YouTube page 
2. Search a video Search for the video you want to convert and copy its link YouTube pageYouTube
" YouTube page 
3. Accessing page Access the official page of Ytmp3 to perform the conversion. Ytmp3 pageYtmp3
" Ytmp3 page 
Copy and paste the link of video Paste the link of the video you copied and click &ldquo;Convert&rdquo;.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to check your water bill debts (Sanasa)</title>
    <link>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-consultar-debitos-sanasa/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 02:04:31 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-consultar-debitos-sanasa/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The Society for Water Supply and Sanitation - Sanasa Campinas was created on August 28, 1974. Sanasa was one of the first sanitation companies in Brazil to add fluoride to the water treatment.
1. Downloading iTunes . Access the official page of Sanasa to check debts. Sanasa pageSanasa
" Sanasa page 
2. Enter the consumer code, you can find it in your account. Sanasa accountSanasa
" Sanasa account]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to make modeling clay at home</title>
    <link>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-fazer-massinha-modelar/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 02:04:05 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-fazer-massinha-modelar/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[We all know that children love to play clay, now imagine they can make their own? And even more the one where all the ingredients are edible !!! That&rsquo;s right, if your child takes the mouth, there will be no problem. You will spend little and I bet that all the ingredients you will have in your home.
1. Ingredients  1 cup of salt 4 cups of flour 1 cup and a half of water 3 colheres de sopa de óleo Food coloring of choice (optional)  Preparation mode 1º step  In a large pot, mix the salt and flour and then add the oil and water.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to Make Homemade Condensed Milk</title>
    <link>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-fazer-leite-condensado/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 02:04:15 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-fazer-leite-condensado/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to make Brigadeiro</title>
    <link>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-fazer-brigadeiro/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 02:03:03 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-fazer-brigadeiro/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[1. Ingredients  1 can of condensed milk 3 tablespoons chocolate 1 teaspoon of butter 1 Chocolate sprinkles  Preparation mode 1º step  In a small saucepan, place the condensed milk, chocolate and butter. Cook over slow heat, always mixing with a wooden spoon, until it is off the bottom of the pan. This is important: when you tilt the pan a little bit, you will notice that the brigadeiro “slides”, leaving the bottom.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to make Churros</title>
    <link>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-fazer-churros/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 02:02:38 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-fazer-churros/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>IR 2020 - How to check if your refund has been released?</title>
    <link>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/imposto-de-renda-2020/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 02:01:51 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/imposto-de-renda-2020/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The Federal Revenue opened on Friday (22) the consultation to the first batch of refunds of Income Tax 2020. The payment will be made on the 29th, in the bank account indicated by the taxpayer when making the declaration. The return schedule was maintained even with the filing of the IR declaration postponed (from 30 April to 30 June)
1. Acessing Receita Federal website To find out if the declaration has been released, the taxpayer must access the Receita Federal website or call Receitafone, at number 146.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to choose the best places to travel in the interior of São Paulo</title>
    <link>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-conhecer-5-lugares-sp/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 01:31:07 -0300</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>http://fazendotudo.com.br/en/como-conhecer-5-lugares-sp/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[5 cities in the interior of São Paulo that you need to know:
1. Campos de Jordão Campos do Jordão is called &ldquo;Brazilian Switzerland&rdquo;, for its late architecture based on European constructions and for its colder climate than the Brazilian average. For this reason, the city receives more tourists both nationally and internationally during the winter season, especially in the month of July.
Campos de JordãoCampos de Jordão
" Campos de Jordão]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
